Guide to the Cable 13 Videotapes, 1976-2009 UA.09.13.0008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0027, 1976-2009; 2
  - Basketball: Duke vs UVA, 1987 February 04 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0329)
    Program Length: 31mins52secs; Cable13 tape number: L13/S1 Tape 2 (2); Other notes:
  - Basketball: Duke vs UVA, 1987 February 04 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0330)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: fans and cheerleaders, switches to football
  - Special Events: Ralph Nader, 1987 February 05 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0331)
  - Special Events: Ralph Nader, 1987 February 05 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0332)
  - The Feud: IFC vs Panhellenic, 1987 February 10 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0333)
    Program Length: 27mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: L14/S4; Other notes: The Cook Premiere, comedy
  - Duke Magazine - Ralph Nader Clips, 1987 February 12 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0334)
    Other notes: Students on Quad, ATO Read Race
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1987 February 14 (Box 43, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0335)
  - Sports Center, 1987 February 15 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0336)
    Cable13 tape number: L 13/56; Other notes: Show #4 w/ Billy & Swimmers
  - Sports Center, 1987 February 22 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0337)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: NBA Slam Dunk Contest, sports highlights, Alan and Cheerleaders
  - Interview w/ Mohamed Malahi - Painter, 1987 February 23 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0338)
  - Mohamed Malahi's Paintings and Music, 1987 February 23 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0339)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1
  - Duke Magazine, 1987 February 24 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0340)
    Other notes: Francis Lynn and NCPIRG
  - Basketball: Duke vs Clemson, 1987 February 28 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0341)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1)
  - Sports Center, 1987 March 01 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0348)
  - Special Events: Dick Gregory, 1987 March 02 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0349)
    Other notes: "The Struggle Continues" Page Auditorium
  - The Feud: Football vs Soccer, 1987 March 03 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0350)
  - Speakers: Maki Mandella, 1987 March 03 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0351)
  - Speakers: Maki Mandella, 1987 March 03 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0352)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: 2nd part of tape #297
  - The Feud: Men's vs Women's Club Lacrosse, 1987 March 07 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0353)
  - Cyrus X, 1987 March 18 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0354)
    Cable13 tape number: #11; Other notes: At the Hideaway
  - Carolina Theater Restoration Documentary, 1987 March 19 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0355)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: 10/10/81 Football (vs. Va. Tech)
  - Carolina Theater Restoration Documentary, 1987 March 19 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0356)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3)
  - Carolina Theater Restoration Documentary, 1987 March 19 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0357)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3)
  - Sports Center, 1987 March 29, 1987 April 05 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0358)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: 3/29 - LAX Players, highlights of b-ball, omega, baseball, tennis, hockey and club LAX, 4/5 Women's golf, tennis, Men's LAX, baseball tribute
  - No Pretensions, 1987 March 30 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0359)
    Program Length: 31mins; Cable13 tape number: #7; Other notes: Jeff's First Show
  - Lacrosse: Duke vs Delaware, 1987 April 01 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0307)
    Cable13 tape number: L13/S6
  - Duke Magazine, 1987 April 04 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0308)
    Cable13 tape number: L 15 / S 3; Other notes: Host: Liz Olrich, Date Rape
  - Dizzy Gillespie-Jazz, 1987 April 04 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0309)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (5)
  - Dizzy Gillespie-Jazz, 1987 April 04 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0310)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 4 (5)
  - Dizzy Gillespie-Jazz, 1987 April 04 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0311)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (5)
  - Dizzy Gillespie-Jazz, 1987 April 04 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0312)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (5)
  - Dizzy Gillespie-Jazz, 1987 April 04 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0313)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 5 (5)
  - No Pretensions, 1987 April 05 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0314)
    Cable13 tape number: #8
  - No Pretensions, 1987 April 09 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0315)
  - Sports Center, 1987 April 12 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0316)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Billy King, Men's and Women's LAX
  - Sports Center, 1987 April 12 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0317)
  - Acoustic Guitar Concert, 1987 April 16 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0318)
    Program Length: `; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Spiedel, Goodrich and Lille, PUB & DUU
  - Sports Center, 1987 April 19 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0319)
  - No Pretensions, 1987 September 15 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0381)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-118; Other notes: Interviews, Med School Brunch, Seduction, Crew: Jeff Bass
  - Special Events: Elie Wiesel, 1987 September 15 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0382)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-117; Other notes: Part 2
  - Special Events: Elie Wiesel, 1987 September 15 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0383)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-066; Other notes: Tape 1 of 2: Second Part on tape# 336
  - Sports Center, 1987 September 20 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0384)
    Program Length: 16mins8secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-067; Other notes: Show #1: Highlights: Colgate and northwestern football, guest-Greg Downs, Dave Colona, Interview w/ Spurrier, Prod: Suzanne White
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1987 September 21 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0385)
    Program Length: 25mins20secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-115
  - Devil Visions #1, 1987 September 22 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0386)
    Program Length: 15mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-121; Other notes: Show #1 Chapel, East, Durham
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1987 September 27 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0387)
    Program Length: 18min4secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-126; Other notes: Show #2: Soccer highlights, Cheerleader interview
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1987 October 04 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0368)
    Program Length: 29mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-131; Other notes: Show #3: Highlights-men's tennis, guests-Rugby players, Producer: Suzanne White
  - Mating Game, 1987 October 08 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0369)
    Program Length: 28mins; Cable13 tape number: #3; Other notes: w/ Pete Cook
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1987 October 11 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0370)
    Program Length: 27mins33secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-133; Other notes: Show #4 Highlights: vollyball, IMF Ball-BOG/Law sch., guests-Volleyball, Prod: Suzanne White, Co-Prod. Josh Leifer
  - Devil Visions #2, 1987 October 12 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0371)
    Program Length: 29mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-132; Other notes: Show #2 Discontinuim of time & space, campus candids, lemurs and such
  - Special Events: Terry Sanford, 1987 October 12 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0372)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-078; Other notes: Tape 1 of 2
  - Special Events: Terry Sanford, 1987 October 12 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0373)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-079; Other notes: Tape 2 of 2
  - Interview w/ Terry Sanford, 1987 October 12 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0374)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-2-036; Other notes: President Honor Council, News Archive Tape
  - Jerry Falwell, 1987 October 15 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0375)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-136; Other notes: Tape #2
  - Sports Center, 1987 October 25 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0376)
    Program Length: 28mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-137; Other notes: Episode #5, Soccer guests, highlights: football, spe3, soccer Produced by Suzanne White
  - Coach K, 1987 October 28 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0377)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-2; Other notes: Tape 2
  - Step Show #44, 1987 October 29 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0378)
    Program Length: 19mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-2-044
  - Alumni Panel, 1987 October 30 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0379)
    Cable13 tape number: 1 of 2; Other notes: #46, Reynolds Price, etc.
  - Alumni Panel, 1987 October 30 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0380)
    Cable13 tape number: 2 of 2; Other notes: #47, Reynolds Price, etc.
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1987 November 01 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0360)
    Program Length: 27mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-074; Other notes: Show #6 guests-Women's B-Ball, Highlights-Football vs GA tech, Blue/White B-Ball, Prod: Suzanne White, Co-Prod: Josh Leifer
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1987 November 01 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0361)
    Program Length: 17mins47secs; Other notes: studio and interview w/ Eisner, CEO Disney, Chuck and Mike
  - Mating Game, 1987 November 05 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0362)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-140; Other notes: Senior Girl Syndrome show, Senior-frosh theme
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1987 November 08 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0363)
    Program Length: 21mins 10secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-139; Other notes: Show #7 guests-Women's tennis, highlights, bloopers Prod-Suzanne White, Co-Prod-Josh Leifer
  - Mating Game, 1987 November 12 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0364)
    Program Length: 31mins; Cable13 tape number: #6; Other notes: w/ Pete Cook
  - The Feud: GA vs. Trent, 1987 November 18 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0365)
  - Sports Center #8, 1987 November 22 (Box 44, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0366)
    Program Length: 29mins7secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-142; Other notes: guests: basketball players Crew: S. White, J. Leifer
  - A.B. "Duke Scholar" Program, 1987 November 23 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0367)
  - Sports Center, 1987 December 06 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0320)
    Program Length: 18mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-144; Other notes: Semester wrap up, guests: Dan on Football, Producer: Suzanne White, Co-Prod: Josh Leifer
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1987 December 06 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0321)
    Program Length: 23mins42secs
  - Student Activities, 1987 December 08, 1987 December 09 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0322)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3; Other notes: Focus on Freewater, Hoof N' Horn, Cable 13, crew: Nick Morns, Steve Tell
  - Mating Game in CI (Live), 1987 December 09 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0323)
    Cable13 tape number: 8705-6-?
  - Battle of the Bands 1988 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0040)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: 8801-6-189; Other notes: Tape 3 (4)
  - Battle of the Bands 1988 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0041)
    Program Length: 36mins; Other notes: Tape 4 (4)
  - Late Night Show w/ S & M, 1988 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0042)
    Other notes: #2 Best of Cyrus
  - Late Night Show w/ S & M, 1988 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0043)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-073; Other notes: #3
  - ASDU Presidential Debate, 1988 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0044)
  - ASDU Presidential Debate, 1988 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0045)
  - 1988 Commencement (Box 46, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0046)
  - Late Night Show w/ S&M, 1988 (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0047)
    Program Length: 44mins50secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-087; Other notes: guests - Billy King, Danny Ferry, Angry Man, Madgy Fareg
  - Hoof 'n Horn, 1988 Fall (Box 53, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0408)
    Program Length: 58mins53secs; Cable13 tape number: 1 of 2; Other notes: A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To the Forum'
  - Night Night #3, 1988 Spring (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0466)
    Program Length: 33mins27secs; Cable13 tape number: 8705-6-164; Other notes: M&D BTSM Show, dirty no good robbing leech, "America" PM magazine, intro "torn pants" sketch, mall man, Pepperidge farm comm. Willful waiter sketch
  - Night Night #4, 1988 Spring (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0467)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: 8801-3-204; Other notes: girlfriend trouble and dinner
  - Night Night the movie "Murphy's Law", 1988 Spring (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0468)
    Program Length: 55mins; Cable13 tape number: 8705-6-170; Other notes: The Story of Murphy Mott, Prod: David Lammey
  - Documentary on "Once Upon a Mattress", 1988 Winter (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0469)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-148; Other notes: filmed, produced, edited by Steve Tell
  - Entry ll Entertainment, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0470)
    Program Length: 16mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-270; Other notes: Show #7
  - Duke Basketball: Tribute to Winningest Class, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0471)
    Cable13 tape number: 8811-60-620; Other notes: Tape 3, Highlights tribute to Ferry, Snyder, Smith Edited: Tim Kelly, Steve Goldberg
  - Cable 13 Sports, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0472)
    Cable13 tape number: 8807-68-252; Other notes: Highlights tape#1 88 - 89
  - Cable 13 Sports, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0473)
    Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-295; Other notes: Highlights tape#2 88 - 89
  - Thelonious Monk Institute of Jazz concert, 1988-1989 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0474)
    Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-265; Other notes: 1 of 2
  - Thelonious Monk Institute of Jazz concert, 1988-1989 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0475)
    Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-321; Other notes: 2 of 2
  - Duke Yearlook, 1988 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0006)
  - Sports Center, 1988 January 17 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0422)
    Program Length: 18mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6; Other notes: Show #10 highlights, St. Louis and MD, B-ball, Dawkins
  - Night Night #2, 1988 January 20 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0423)
    Program Length: 37mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-105; Other notes: Almost Live from The Bread n' Board Cafe©, Crew, Jim, Marcheta
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1988 January 24 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0424)
    Program Length: 15mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-064; Other notes: Show #11
  - News Archive Tape, 1988 January 25 (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0425)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-116; Other notes: Dan & Arches
  - Late Edition & Reagan Show and Debate, 1988 January 27, 1988 February 08 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0426)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-071; Other notes: Dan and Sucheg, #1 Mon night
  - Sportsline #1, 1988 February 05 (Box 46, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0409)
    Program Length: 34mins; Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-260; Other notes: KA vs power tools, prod: Mark Mayer
  - Sports Center, 1988 February 05, 1989 February 12 (Box 44, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0410)
    Program Length: 25mins&12mins; Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-268; Other notes: 2/12/89 at 25:00 on tape
  - Sports Center, 1988 February 07 (Box 42, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0411)
    Program Length: 27mins; Cable13 tape number: 8801-2-231; Other notes: Show #12 highlights: Men's and Women's Basketball, Ice Hockey
  - Reagan's News and Debate, 1988 February 08 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0412)
    Program Length: 6mins; Cable13 tape number: 8705-6; Other notes: Show tape
  - Rock for Homeless: Duke Homeless Project, 1988 February 08 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0413)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-135; Other notes: Late Edition Show
  - Hoof n' Horn: "Once Upon a Mattress", 1988 February 13 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0414)
    Program Length: 58mins; Cable13 tape number: 8801-6-191; Other notes: Tape 1 of 3, a musical
  - Hoof n' Horn: "Once Upon a Mattress", 1988 February 13 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0415)
    Program Length: 54mins15mins; Cable13 tape number: 8801-6-192; Other notes: Tape 2 of 3, a musical
  - Hoof n' Horn: "Once Upon a Mattress", 1988 February 13 (Box 40, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0416)
    Program Length: 8mins 15secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-153; Other notes: Tape 3 of 3, a musical
  - Devil Visions #4, 1988 February 16 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0417)
    Program Length: 33mins35secs; Cable13 tape number: 8801-6-181; Other notes: Show #4 Conversation about sexual assault, underwater fun, perspectives on dream and film
  - Basketball: Duke vs Virginia Cavaliers, 1988 February 17 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0418)
    Program Length: 55mins58secs; Cable13 tape number: 8705-6-179; Other notes: Tape 2
  - Duke vs Virginia, 1988 February 17 (Box 52, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0419)
    Cable13 tape number: 8705-6-178
  - Sports Center, 1988 February 21 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0420)
    Program Length: 25mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-150; Other notes: Show #13
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1988 February 21, 1988 February 07 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0421)
    Program Length: 28mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-149; Other notes: 2/21 00-16:00, 2/7 16:00-28:30
  - Sports Center #14, 1988 March 20 (Box 44, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0429)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-151
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1988 March 27 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0430)
    Program Length: 15mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-155; Other notes: Show #15
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1988 March 27 (Box 43, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0431)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-147
  - Devil Visions #5, 1988 April 04 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0399)
    Program Length: 48mins; Cable13 tape number: 8705-6-161; Other notes: Show #5 Easy answers, substance abuse
  - Abbie Hoffman, 1988 April 06 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0400)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: Speech in Page (tech services dub)
  - Abbie Hoffman, 1988 April 06 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0401)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3); Other notes: Speech in Page (tech services dub)
  - Abbie Hoffman, 1988 April 06 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0402)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: Speech in Page (tech services dub)
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1988 April 10 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0403)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-156; Other notes: Show #16 Kevin/Billy, Basketball Homecoming, Duke Students
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1988 April 17 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0404)
    Program Length: 29mins; Cable13 tape number: 8801-3-201; Other notes: Show #16 guests: Lacrosse
  - Passing the Quarter, 1988 April 22 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0405)
    Program Length: 47mins; Other notes: A collection of famous musical numbers with a common theme sung by students from Drama and Hoot n' Horn. The senior recital of Philip J. Santora. Crew: Steve Tell
  - Devil Visions #6, 1988 June 15 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0427)
    Program Length: 29mins; Cable13 tape number: 8801-3-205; Other notes: Show #6 A dream away, where the streets have no name, untitled
  - Soccer Demo Championship, 1988 June 22 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0428)
    Program Length: 15mins; Cable13 tape number: L13/S3; Other notes: Highlights from 1986 Men's Soccer Team Duke's 1st National Championship
  - American Dream: Montel Williams, 1988 August 05 (Box 46, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0406)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: inspirational speech
  - News Archive Tape: Jessie Jackson, 1988 August 28 (Box 101, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0407)
    Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-310; Other notes: in Cameron, Reel 2
  - Weekend Update, 1988 September 18 (Box 43, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0461)
    Program Length: 5mins; Cable13 tape number: 8804-20-237; Other notes: News spoof, comedy, guest: Joe Nerdermeyer Prod: Matt Anderson
  - Inside Duke, 1988 September 21 (Box 42, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0462)
    Program Length: 48mins; Cable13 tape number: Show #1; Other notes: First Broadcast: Jesse Jackson, Student Action Week, Duke Drama, James D. Barber, Book of Questions, Hosts: Peter Cook, Jennifer Blaser
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1988 September 25 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0463)
    Program Length: 26mins26secs; Cable13 tape number: 8801-30-212; Other notes: "A Look Back at SCS 1987-88" including: Tough boys, Billy does the weather, Playing w/ the boys, Rugby, Blue Devil, Hockey, Footers, tribute to Billy and Kevin, Prod: Suzanne White
  - Interviews w/ Lydia Crews, 1988 September 28 (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0464)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-070; Other notes: Part 1 - interview w/ Lydia Crews, Nelson Matusow, Rebecca Cooper, Daniliff Part 2 - Panel w/ Jack Nelson, Barbara Matusow, Nicholas Daniloff
  - Bull Session, 1988 September 29 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0465)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-288; Other notes: Show #2, Leifer
  - Inside Duke, 1988 October 05 (Box 42, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0444)
    Program Length: 33mins; Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-300; Other notes: Show #2 Prod: M. Hitti, P. Hirschkorn Women's Coalition, Parking, Interview w/ Carol and Eric Myers, Questions, 1968 Vigil Reunion Hosts: Adam MacManus, Jane Rinzler
  - Bull Session, 1988 October 06 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0445)
    Program Length: 31mins; Cable13 tape number: Show 3; Other notes: Election Discussion, Host: Geoff Mason w/ Ron Temple, Walter Keay, David Pyle, Seth Davis
  - Sports Center Sunday #2, 1988 October 09 (Box 44, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0446)
    Program Length: 19mins21secs; Cable13 tape number: 8801-30-214; Other notes: Prod: S. White, Anthony Dilwes interview, women's and men's soccer
  - Entry ll Entertainment, 1988 October 12 (Box 42, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0447)
    Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-243; Other notes: Show #2
  - Sports Center Sunday #3, 1988 October 12 (Box 44, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0448)
    Program Length: 57mins26secs; Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-250; Other notes: Men's b-ball Cable 13 Sports Event
  - Trinity Feud: BEN vs House of Girls, 1988 October 13 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0449)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8807-30-423; Other notes: Episode #2, Produced by Dan Treinish
  - Bull Session, 1988 October 20 (Box 41, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0450)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8807-60-294; Other notes: Show #4 Political Discussion Election '88